Isai Pavlov

SENIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER || MERN

Details

Kyiv, Ukraine live:.cid.ffa70d5eadb43221 passiongod1@gmail.com

Skills

JavaScript: ES6,ES7,ES8

TypeScript

Angular

React.js

Next.js

HTML5

CSS3/SASS/BootStrap

Node

PHP

Python

MySQL

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

REST API

GraphQL

Docker

Languages

Russian

English

Hobbies

Running, Swimming, Basketball

Profile

Enthusiastic software engineer with 8+ years of experience participating in the complete product development lifecycle of successfully launched applications. Owns strong debugging and troubleshooting skills that allow me to quickly analyze problems and come to a modern solution that extends the life of the application without rewriting everything from scratch. Specialized in web application development such as E-Commerce System, Enterprise App, Single Page Application, Health Care System, Learning Management System.

These are my skills:

- TypeScript, JavaScript
- React.js, Redux, React Hooks, Styled Components, Next.js
- Vue, Vuex, Vuetify Angular, NgRX, RxJS, Angular Material, Angular Universal
- Ionic Framework, React Native, Cordova, PhoneGap
- Node.js, PHP, Laravel, ExpressJS, Python/Django, ASP.NET, C#, MSSQL
- HTML, HTML5, CSS, CSS3, Bootstrap 3/4/5 WordPress/Shopify
- Git, Github, Bitbucket, Gitlab Firebase | FireStore, AWS, Heroku, Jira, Trello, Asana, Clubhouse
- Figma, Zeplin, PSD, Sketch These are my abilities:
- 40+ hours work per week, Available to start work immediately
- Daily update using Git
- Clean and Efficient code Positive attitude, Hard Working, Quick Learning
- 12+ hours online on Freelancer

Employment History

Expert Front-end Developer | Thinkover

June 2014 - March 2015

- Designed the application architecture.
- •Led the front-end development. •Implemented visual design solutions (Zeplin).
- •Visualized several data structures using D3.js.
- •Introduced Sass style guides for a responsive design.

Technologies: D3.js, TypeScript, Angular

Front-end Developer | Paladin

July 2015 - January 2016

- •Implemented a mobile-first responsive design.
- •Introduced style guides to the project.
- •Improved the overall user experience.

Technologies: Django, Bootstrap

Senior Front-end Developer | Goreha

March 2016 - April 2017

- •Led the front-end development of a multi-lingual digital rehabilitation platform.
- •Used Angular 5 and NgRx to make the Reactive front end.
- Migrated and merged an admin panel application into the platform.
- •Built from scratch a product website with React and GatsbyJS.

Technologies: Bootstrap, Angular Material, NgRx, Angular

Front-end Developer | Softimation LTD

- •Finished implementing a cryptocurrency exchange built using Angular.
- Handled the pixel-perfect implementation of the specs (Zeplin).
- •Used Angular animations to improve the overall UX.
- •Converted a web app to a native version using Cordova.
- •Transformed the app to be mobile-first and fully responsive.

Technologies: NgRx, Angular

React Developer | BCG GAMMA

August 2018 - March 2019

- Developed a prototype used to visualize transportation routes using React, Antd, and Deck.gl.
- •Built a scheduling tool in the form of a Gantt chart using React and Material-UI.
- •Researched and selected libraries and tools.
- •Balanced requirements, UX, and deadlines in order to get most of the business value in a limited timeframe.
- Designed APIs and manipulated big data.
- Composed scripts—with Python and Node.js—to parse complex data structures.

Technologies: Node.js, Recharts, Python, Deck.gl, React

Full-stack Developer | Avatar Engines LLC

July 2019 - April 2020

- •Worked on providing API endpoints with Node.js/Inversify and MongoDB.
- •Built from scratch admin platform for managing platform's database entities and users using React, Node.js, and Mongoose.
- •Implemented complex UI components with React/TypeScript and SCSS.
- •Improved the UX by creating several DnD-based components.
- Wrote scripts to use and manipulate data from various sources.

Technologies: MongoDB, Node.js, React

Education

Kyiv State University of Technology and Design

Bachelor of Computer Science (BCompSc), Computer science 2009-2013

University of Belgrade

Master of Computer Science (MSCS), Faculty of Mathematics 2016-2018

Other Experiences

Software Development, Project Management Professional (PMP), OCJP6, Certified Scrum Master, Front-end Development, Cloud, AWS, Adobe LiveCycle Enterprise Suite, OpenGL Tablets